[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 6, "question": "Oh, my god, do you think it's him?", "question_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "my", "god", ",", "do", "you", "think", "it", "'s", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 7, "answer": "Put your hands up, and no one will get hurt.", "answer_tokens": ["Put", "your", "hands", "up", ",", "and", "no", "one", "will", "get", "hurt", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "What has come out so far?", "question_tokens": ["What", "has", "come", "out", "so", "far", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "It seems that at least from some of the people we have spoken to around here that both brothers occasionally spent time at this very apartment behind me.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "seems", "that", "at", "least", "from", "some", "of", "the", "people", "we", "have", "spoken", "to", "around", "here", "that", "both", "brothers", "occasionally", "spent", "time", "at", "this", "very", "apartment", "behind", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "What was the demeanor of these three suspects, would you say?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "demeanor", "of", "these", "three", "suspects", ",", "would", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "Piers, they all looked a little bit nervous when they were brought in.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "they", "all", "looked", "a", "little", "bit", "nervous", "when", "they", "were", "brought", "in", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "What do you make of it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "I think that's right.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "'s", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "Why is that so significant?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "that", "so", "significant", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "Well, it just shows the nature of their relationship.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "just", "shows", "the", "nature", "of", "their", "relationship", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 149, "question": "Is there enough in totality, do you think, to suggest a wider conspiracy in the Boston marathon bombings?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "enough", "in", "totality", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "to", "suggest", "a", "wider", "conspiracy", "in", "the", "Boston", "marathon", "bombings", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "RB", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 150, "answer": "Police investigations, criminal investigations, a long road of speculation interrupted by moments of clarification.", "answer_tokens": ["Police", "investigations", ",", "criminal", "investigations", ",", "a", "long", "road", "of", "speculation", "interrupted", "by", "moments", "of", "clarification", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Boston"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "But what is your view about where the balance should be struck between an individual's right to civil liberty and between the right to go after terrorists and catch them?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "is", "your", "view", "about", "where", "the", "balance", "should", "be", "struck", "between", "an", "individual", "'s", "right", "to", "civil", "liberty", "and", "between", "the", "right", "to", "go", "after", "terrorists", "and", "catch", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "Well, in terms of this particular case, I think it's being handled very well.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "in", "terms", "of", "this", "particular", "case", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "being", "handled", "very", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "CD", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 196, "question": "Or is there something a lot more sinister going on?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "is", "there", "something", "a", "lot", "more", "sinister", "going", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "EX", "NN", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "JJ", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 197, "answer": "Well, I think calling them three kids who tried to help a friend trivializes it a bit.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "calling", "them", "three", "kids", "who", "tried", "to", "help", "a", "friend", "trivializes", "it", "a", "bit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "NNS", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 213, "question": "So you have to imagine that they knew that the Vaseline was potentially a key piece of evidence, and that takes them away, I am sure, everyone would think this, from being the kids, the teenagers trying to help friends, into a much more serious situation, doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "have", "to", "imagine", "that", "they", "knew", "that", "the", "Vaseline", "was", "potentially", "a", "key", "piece", "of", "evidence", ",", "and", "that", "takes", "them", "away", ",", "I", "am", "sure", ",", "everyone", "would", "think", "this", ",", "from", "being", "the", "kids", ",", "the", "teenagers", "trying", "to", "help", "friends", ",", "into", "a", "much", "more", "serious", "situation", ",", "does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", ",", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "Well, they don't necessarily have to have been specialists themselves.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "do", "n't", "necessarily", "have", "to", "have", "been", "specialists", "themselves", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "Is it likely they have got it, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "likely", "they", "have", "got", "it", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "I don't know whether it's likely or not.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "whether", "it", "'s", "likely", "or", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 238, "question": "What is your reading of it from an FBI point of view?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "reading", "of", "it", "from", "an", "FBI", "point", "of", "view", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 239, "answer": "They sure are.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "sure", "are", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["FBI"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "I mean, you piece all that together, it's pretty damning, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "you", "piece", "all", "that", "together", ",", "it", "'s", "pretty", "damning", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "It is pretty damning.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "pretty", "damning", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "Who, me?", "question_tokens": ["Who", ",", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ",", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "Yes, (EXPLETIVE DELETED) you.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "(", "EXPLETIVE", "DELETED", ")", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 288, "question": "Have you read your (EXPLETIVE DELETED) jihad?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "read", "your", "(", "EXPLETIVE", "DELETED", ")", "jihad", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "So, I'm not a radical --", "answer_tokens": ["So", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "a", "radical", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "Why do you think he did this?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "think", "he", "did", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "Well, because I'm a Muslim.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "because", "I", "'m", "a", "Muslim", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "As a Muslim, as a proud American as well, how do you feel about that?", "question_tokens": ["As", "a", "Muslim", ",", "as", "a", "proud", "American", "as", "well", ",", "how", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "IN", "RB", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "Really I feel really angry and frustration.", "answer_tokens": ["Really", "I", "feel", "really", "angry", "and", "frustration", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "VBN", "RB", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "Were you not tempted to hit him back and deal with him properly?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "not", "tempted", "to", "hit", "him", "back", "and", "deal", "with", "him", "properly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "Actually, that's the way I handle -- as we said, I'm well- trained physically and tough-trained.", "answer_tokens": ["Actually", ",", "that", "'s", "the", "way", "I", "handle", "--", "as", "we", "said", ",", "I", "'m", "well-", "trained", "physically", "and", "tough-trained", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "Ben, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Ben", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "Doing well.", "answer_tokens": ["Doing", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Oklahoma City"]}, "docId": "130501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "What is your view?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "view", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "I'm not surprised by this, because I think after Oklahoma City, we didn't know exactly how to use technology to our advantage to fight terrorists around the world.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "surprised", "by", "this", ",", "because", "I", "think", "after", "Oklahoma", "City", ",", "we", "did", "n't", "know", "exactly", "how", "to", "use", "technology", "to", "our", "advantage", "to", "fight", "terrorists", "around", "the", "world", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 394, "question": "Would you see that as a new infringement on your civil liberties?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "see", "that", "as", "a", "new", "infringement", "on", "your", "civil", "liberties", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 395, "answer": "No, I see that as criminal profiling.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "see", "that", "as", "criminal", "profiling", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "What is the difference?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "difference", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "I didn't -- well, I didn't advocate for a background check, Piers, on fireworks.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "n't", "--", "well", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "advocate", "for", "a", "background", "check", ",", "Piers", ",", "on", "fireworks", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "What is the difference between that scenario and somebody being suspicious buying fireworks?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "difference", "between", "that", "scenario", "and", "somebody", "being", "suspicious", "buying", "fireworks", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "How many -- well, I will say this.", "answer_tokens": ["How", "many", "--", "well", ",", "I", "will", "say", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "RP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 460, "question": "-- indiscriminately before people wake up and go that's enough kids shooting guns and being shot with guns, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["--", "indiscriminately", "before", "people", "wake", "up", "and", "go", "that", "'s", "enough", "kids", "shooting", "guns", "and", "being", "shot", "with", "guns", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "RP", "CC", "VB", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 461, "answer": "Piers, 170 adults last month ran over children because they didn't look in their rear-view mirror.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "170", "adults", "last", "month", "ran", "over", "children", "because", "they", "did", "n't", "look", "in", "their", "rear-view", "mirror", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130501pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 502, "question": "What is your theory about what would have caused a 747 to go into this extraordinary rapid plunge like this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "theory", "about", "what", "would", "have", "caused", "a", "747", "to", "go", "into", "this", "extraordinary", "rapid", "plunge", "like", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "CD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "Piers, one of the things about coming up with a theory this early in an investigation is that it's probably going to be wrong.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "one", "of", "the", "things", "about", "coming", "up", "with", "a", "theory", "this", "early", "in", "an", "investigation", "is", "that", "it", "'s", "probably", "going", "to", "be", "wrong", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]